# **Kelton Leach**

Full stack Web Dev Student

Bellingham, WA (360) 224-7259 kelton.leach@gmail.com https://github.com/Keltonlea

### **ABOUT ME**

I am currently in a coding bootcamp via University of Washington and have gained experience in HTML, CSS, Javascript, jQuery, Bootstrap, the MERN stack, MYSQL, databases, and git. I work well on my own and in our group projects- I can take lead if needed and also work well with those that like to take lead. When I'm done working I take initiative and find more work that needs to be done, or bugs that need fixing. I am very friendly and social, have a sense of humor, patient, and find that it is important to build a community and work together.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Whatcom Museum, Bellingham, WA — Customer Services Coordinator, museum store manager and buyer

November 2010 - 2015

While managing and buying for the museum store I doubled the store's profits by research and knowledge of demographics and appealing to specific target markets. I traveled to trade shows across the nation and worked with over 100 vendors in the form of wholesale, consignment agreements, and establishing rights to art pieces for reproduction. I am also in charge of customer service; I believe making customers happy is a key factor in the success of a business. I also took on visitor service responsibilities, which included compiled reports of where customers are visiting from, their opinions from our comments books, and graphing high visitor times in comparison to featured exhibits. I also coordinated the history cruise, one of the museum's largest annual events.

### Squat and Gobble Crepery, San Francisco, CA — Server

September 2008 -July 2010

Great team player, barista, bartender, balancing cashier and server duties in a fast-paced, crowded environment.

**EDUCATION** 

### **SKILLS**

intelligent

People Skills/Group Work Leadership Experience Persevering Organized **Problem Solver Customer Service Skills Time Management** empathetic/emotionally

# **University of Washington,** Coding Bootcamp - Full Stack Web Developer

Expected September 2022

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, responsive design, Bootstrap, React, Node.JS, Jquery

# **Washington State University** — Social Sciences, Minor in Business

August 2010 - June 2013

Concentrations in Political Science, Psychology, and Sociology

## **Foothill College** — *Los Altos, CA*

August 2006 - May 2008

### **University of Tennessee** — Chattanooqa, TN

August 2004 - May 2005

#### **Future**

After my current coding bootcamp I plan on taking more courses on programming languages such as Python, java, and C# to continue to gain knowledge in order to advance my passion in web development.